Visit turkision.com for more!
Are our alps in the arena ready? We
shouldn't let them feel even our shadows.
They are ready. Everything
is set as you ordered.
They're waiting for us.
It's time to ruin the enemy's plans, huh?
Yes.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
-You stay here.
-As my Bey orders.
Where does this way lead to?
To The Red Apple?
What is the destination?
Martyrdom!
What will you reach?
Homeland!
Where is the homeland?
The whole world!
May the world be your homeland!
May the universe be your companion!
May your cause be blessed!
Welcome, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Well, well... The emperor must be scared.
Look.
He's built a wall of flesh everywhere.
We'll just watch for now.
We're waiting for the princess to come.
Well...
People are expecting her.
No news from the princess?
There may be something up.
Soldiers are standing on alert.
They'd take action if there
were something wrong.
Even Mongolians are just coming.
Princess is going to arrive shortly.
But we should be cautious, anyway.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
The enemy was a fire around us.
And we were woods in the middle.
So we sat.
Let the enemy be the fire.
Let us be the woods in the middle.
As long as the sky doesn't collapse...
...and the solid ground isn't pierced
...who can break the land
and the morals of Turks?
-You're right my Bey.
-You're right.
Thank you.
Sit down, Osman Bey.
Are your alps on duty?
As you ordered, I sent my alps...
...after Princess Maria to Constantinople.
When are they going to take action?
It's very hard to make a move in Constantinople.
If we wait for it until Konya,
..it will be too late. For this reason,
...I want to take the princess on the way.
Well thought, Osman Bey.
Mongolians should never have the princess!
Okay, okay. What if...
If we fail to take the princess
and the enemy have her,
...what will happen then?
Then may Allah help us.
We all had a sigh of relief when
the Ilkhanid State chose Islam.
But even before we could breathe out,
...they tried to choke us.
Byzantine and Mongolians are
having an alliance with this marriage.
-Their only purpose...
-Will be to destroy us.
Then we won't fail.
Well... To make such an alliance
who is the princess marrying?
That's the matter, Osman Bey.
Emir Coban's nephew who he
appreciates like his own son. Gorklu Khan.
Gorklu Khan, huh?
Gorklu Khan...
He himself is coming to
Konya to take the princess.
Alright.
Don't be worrying. We will
be victorious with Allah's will.
Then..
I need to go back to my duty. Excuse me now.
Sit down.
We didn't invite you to give you information
Osman Bey. We use messengers for that.
We have a more important matter.
People of Rome! Your waiting is ending soon!
Our magnificent princess Maria will salute you!
Well, well... Here comes the princess.
-Long live the princess!
-Princess Maria!
Long live Princess Maria!
My dear people! You've come
from all the way around Byzantine!
-I salute you!
-Long live!
May Jesus Christ be with you!
Come on! Let the feast continue!
If this wedding is done..
Byzantine would be a great trouble to us.
We need to stop it one way or another.
Let us infiltrate them, my bey.
It will be like that. Good job, my valiant.
First let the caravan of princess
be prepared, then you have the duty.
As you command, my bey.
Can you tell me about Tabriz, Mongol?
Are people there harsh like you?
The only thing that keeps
Mongols alive, in the deadly..
Cold of steppes is war, princess.
That is why every Mongol is harsh and a warrior.
I guessed as much.
That is why these showmen
will come with me for my wedding.
If I can not stay at Constantinople,
I will take its magnificence with me.
You will be a bride to Amir Choban, Princess.
This is a dream of many hatuns of tribe.
You will see greater versions of these shows.
I know. However, the real show..
Will begin when we expel
Turks from our lands forever.
We've been watching you
for all these years, Osman Bey.
You did not do wrong, stained
your honor or fell for tricks..
You answered truthfully to everything.
Thank Allah, thank Allah, thank Allah.
However, we still waited. This
valiant called "Osman Bey"..
Is after his own gain or the order of the world.
We wanted to see for the last time.
We saw and believed. We came to a decision.
Build your sovereign Beylic now, Osman Bey.
Praise be!
Thank Glorious Allah..
Who does not hold us responsible with victory..
But with the road itself.
Nobles of my land..
Have seen me fit for this big duty.
May you live long.
May Allah be my witness;
My country and my people..
Will always remain free.
What about other beylics? Candar..
Karasids, Hamidids.
They used to follow
Germiyanids. What will they say?
Do you know how Yakup Bey
made beys follow him, Osman Bey?
By putting daggers to each of their privacy.
By threatening them with their
lives and making them bow.
Yakup Bey.
-Yakup Bey.
-May the crooked sword..
Rust in its sheathe.
May you walk your path, Osman Bey.
Thank you. It will be like
that, as you commanded.
Now, the path is clear. Those
who will walk it also clear.
The state that will unit Turks, is clear.
May it be Gokturks, Seljuks.
Turks always have their country.
Turks always have a state.
Now, it is time to be State of Osman!
Praise be!
May your state be glorious, Osman Bey!
Ameen.
May Glorious Allah be my
witness I will always stand firm.
I will build a great country..
That will be a home to the whole world..
And will be under the
shadow of the banner of Islam.
Then, hear one of the secrets
of Turks' state, Osman Bey.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the compassionate.
Our Allah commands in the Al-Qasas Surah..
"That eternaT Home in the Hereafter..
We reserve only1 for those who seek neither
tyranny nor corruption on the earth..
The ultimate outcome belongs
only' to the righteous." [28:83]
Allah almighty told the truth.
-May your cause be glorious, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
May you live long.
For sure, our cause is holy.
Nokers, Horseman ready the field.
Sacrifices too. Everything will be
ready when Gorklu Khan comes.
If anyone makes a
mistake I will take your lives.
That is me.
Mergen. What do you see?
Blood, blood, blood!
Blood you say? That blood will be Osman's blood.
When Gorklu Khan weds the princess..
The army of Rome will be under our
command. Turk blood will be spilled!
Rivers of it!
Mergen, speak.
The grand Mongol state
will be built on Turk blood.
That is what I see!
Thank You, my Allah.. My Allah...
Thank You...
Thanks to Allah...
Boran! -My Bey!
Now we are free!
We will declare our independence!
My Bey, what are you saying?
Konya, Mongols...
...and Yakub...It will be harder for them.
Either we will disappear for our independence...
..or we will establish..
...a great state that will last forever!
Come on. Inform Kayi's Beys.
I want to host them all in my council.
Only Kayi Beys, my Bey?
From now on, we will walk
with people who are on our side...
...not with people who we believe
to be on our side. Only Kayi's Beys.
Come on. Go to Yenisehir.
Send a messenger, Boran.
-My Osman Bey..
Thanks to my Allah..
Go now. Send a messenger.
My Bey, where will you go?
I will go to...
...my father Ertugrul Ghazi
to give him the good news.
Yes my Bey. Yes my Bey.
I
f
*5 , \'
Princess' caravan will be
prepared! Where are the carriers?
The trader came. Hurry. Come on.
Konur Bey... If I didn't know about your past...
...I would think you were a different person.
Is that so? You don't seem
normal either, Bayindir Bey.
Come on.
This will be done as soon as
possible! Hurry, you stupid people!
Where have you been you stupid men?
I will make you pay for it if you do
not prepare the caravan on time. Hurry!
Trader Sergio. The caravan had to be ready.
Commander Ducas... It is ready.
It will be ready but... -It will be done...
...before the sun sets in Constantinople.
Do you understand? -Yes.
I understand, Commander Dukas.
Hurry! Come on, you stupid men!
Trader Sergio... Why are
we in a rush for the caravan?
We need to do an
outstanding job for the Princess.
My goods are already outstanding, idiot.
Princess must set out as soon as
possible so Byzantium can get rid of Turks.
Sure... May holy Jesus help them.
Don't worry. We will prepare the caravan.
Where will we bring the
caravan after it is ready?
Have it prepared first, then you
will take it to the inn behind the arena.
Then you will set out from there.
Sure, if they have a route. What good can come
from the route planned at the last moment?
Saadet Hatun calls Holofira her
"daughter-in-law" Alaeddin. Daughter in law.
We cannot be sure before
we listen to Holofira, brother.
Holofira will never say yes to Mehmet.
If she doesn't become a Muslim, it
will be hard to convince Malhun mother.
She will. She will accept
becoming a Muslim. If she does not...
..then I will abduct her.
Stop, brother... You
need to talk to Holofira first.
I can go and ask Gonca Hatun
without letting her know, huh?
So you will sound Gonca out, huh?
Look at you... You are looking
for an excuse to talk to that Hatun.
That Hatun is looking for a way to escape
when she sees you. How will you talk to her?
And that is my secret, brother.
If Holofira says yes, it will be
really hard to control Orhan.
We must find a bride as soon as possible.
Ulgen, you are the one who
can do this in the best way.
The things we heard from others were not useful.
Look around carefully, and find us a good bride.
Don't worry. I will find good-hearted
brides for our Shahzades.
You don't like Gonca, I see
that. But I don't know why.
You will give me the answer of it today, Ulgen.
Good news! Good news!
Osman Bey is now independent!
No one can stand in his way now!
What happened Boran Bey? May it be good.
The elders of Turks allowed us...
Now we are an independent Beylic, Alhamdulillah.
Alhamdulillah.
We are one step closer to our
blessed dream, huh? Thanks to Allah!
Thanks to Him, He let us see these days.
Thanks to Allah!
My Allah, I seek refuge in
You from the accursed shaitaan.
In the name of Allah, the Most
Gracious, the Most Merciful.
My father... My ancestor...
My Bey...
I have good news for you.
Your dreams... Our dreams..
...have come true.
With Allah's consent, from now on we will be...
...a sovereign and an independent Beylic
You fought against the cruel.
You got over many hardships, but...
But I followed you without losing my way.
I know it will be harder now.
Now, our responsibilities will be heavier.
I know that Allah is letting
us rule and testing our justice.
Allah is giving us power and testing our mercy.
And...
And the burden of the state on my shoulders...
Father...
I am afraid of not being able to stand it.
Father... The people are entrusted to me now.
Our future is entrusted to me now.
The fortune of a nation
the history of a nation..
...is now entrusted to me.
There is no one we depend on,
there is no one behind us anymore.
We are alone now.
You taught me, father, you would say...
..."If the burden is too
heavy to carry for you...
...then..
...stand up for the nation, for the
state." "When the issues grow...
...a brave heart is always better
than a sharp sword", you would say.
For sure, for sure we are courageous enough.
Whether we are few or many,
the conquests will never stop.
We will fly the sanjak of
Islam everywhere in the world.
Alhamdulillah..
Alhamdulillah... My father..
It was entrusted from you to me...
...and from me to my children. You
don't have to worry about it anymore.
Ertugrul Ghazi.
My Allah, the Owner of all
the properties. Thank you.
You made us live these days, thank you.
My Allah, let us serve the Islam tomorrow
just like we did in the past and today.
Grant us the ability to
rule with justice and mercy.
Come on sisters, come on!
Today is a blessed day, let's hurry.
It is great, right, mother?
My Rabb let us see these days, thankfully.
The majestic plane tree is taking root.
It is flourishing before our eyes.
And we're witnessing it.
May Allah make us all worthy of it.
Aameen.
My Shahzade
is there anything missing? If there is,
let me go to the marketplace and buy it.
So I can see Gonca Hatun.
No, you will help us outside.
I said I want to see Gonca Hatun.
But if you don't get how a lover feels.
We do. We understand.
We understand you the best, Ghazi Alp.
I know you, my Shahzade, but who
is Shahzade Alaeddin in love with?
You... You wrote that letter
to Gonca Hatun, is that so?
Be quiet Ghazi, one should not
let everyone talk about his lover.
We're rivals now, Alaeddin Bey!
Keep it in your mind!
-My Shahzade.
-Ghazi Alp.
Look at him.
Alaeddin, I told you. Your
biggest rival is Ghazi Alp.
-He's not an easy rival.
-He almost drew the sword.
They left you, I set you free.
I expect you to serve
your state and your nation.
Go to Yenisehir, they're waiting for you.
Come on. Give the good news.
You called me, Bala Hatun.
You ran away from me in the marketplace, Ulgen.
Now tell me what you're hiding.
What do you know about Gonca?
-Bala Hatun, I don't know anything.
-Ulgen.
Don't lie to me. There's
something but you're not telling me.
Now tell me.
Shahzade Alaeddin and
Gonca Hatun cannot be together.
They can't, because...
...Gonca loves somebody else.
What are you saying, Ulgen?
I thought Gonca was playing
tricks on us with her family.
Are you sure about it? Did Gonca tell you?
No. I heard it from the hatuns close to her.
Thank you Ulgen.
What a terrible lie I've told.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
-May I come in, my Sultan?
-Come in.
My Sultan, we have news from
Yenisehir, from Cerkutay Bey.
Osman.
What's going on, Yakup Bey?
Osman. Osman.
Father, what's going on?
-Osman is forming his sovereign Beylic.
-What?
He's showing his teeth.
He's challenging us.
How could he do this without asking you, father?
How dare Osman do this, Yakup Bey?
Establishing his sovereign
Beylic will cause conflict.
It will! It will cause conflict.
If there is the slightest separation or problem,
they will immediately go to Osman.
But I will not let it happen.
I will break the person who
separates, I will cut the problem.
Who are you to become a Sultan, Osman?
-Kanyumaz.
-My Sultan.
Send messengers to Beys. I want
them all to come before me tonight.
Yes, my Sultan.
-Mehmed.
Inform the spies around Yenisehir
and tell them to keep their eyes open.
Let us be aware of even
the flying bird. We will know
what's Osman doing and who is with him.
Yes, father.
Osman
Come here.
BismillahirRahmanirRahim.
-My father.
-Give it to me.
Our dream is coming true, father.
That's right, children.
The journey that my ancestor Suleyman Shah
and my ancestor Ertugrul Ghazi
took from the Caspian Sea to Ahlat
and from Ahlat to Aleppo in pursuit of a dream
has now become real.
-Thankfully.
-Thankfully, my Bey. Kayi is free now.
It is free.
It is time to take root.
We have a long way to
go, the world is big, my Bey.
Our roots will be here but the branches
will spread around the world
thanks to you and your children.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
-Let it cover the world...
-...and shelter the innocent people, my Bey.
-We will advance as long as we breathe, my Bey.
We will advance for sure. But the path is tough.
It's not right to walk alone.
Alaeddin.
Tell me, how's your love affair going?
Orhan, what about you?
-My Bey.
-We'll handle it, my Bey.
We'll handle it and we
will make the state prosper.
-And we will take what's in our heart, I hope.
-I hope so.
I want you to show this courage
before Holofira as well, brother.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, all the beys of Kayi
are here, they're waiting for you.
We've been waiting for
this moment for a long time.
Welcome. Welcome.
Do you know about the situation?
Osman Bey has declared his sovereign Beylic.
If you hadn't doubted and stood behind him
and if you hadn't given him power
he wouldn't have dared to boast and do this.
If such a separation is taking place today
you are all responsible for this.
So you didn't do anything, is that so
Sultan Yakup?
Whatever I did, I did it for the sake
of my nation. What did Osman do?
They survived thanks to us.
Do you think Mongols and
Byzantium will let them live
when they hear they have been separated?
It will be a pity for his people.
Now you will hear the new laws.
Each of you will arm three thousand alps...
...and send them to the east.
Increase the number of
patrols. Our borders will be clear.
Kanyumaz.
Alps, bring the gold.
These are the coins...
..we've collected in the frontier market so far.
The salaries of 3000 alps...
...will be paid by me.
And you will share the rest.
As for the taxes, I've
remitted the taxes this year.
Long live the Sultan!
-Thank you, my Sultan!
-Long live the Sultan!
Thank you, my Sultan.
-Beys...
The burden of the war will be heavy.
Send your alps to their duties.
Arm the rest.
We will perform raids on Byzantine as before.
As thirsty for battle as the first
day when we stepped on this land.
And as ambitious as the first day!
But this time...
...you will have Great Germiyan's support.
-Thank you, my Sultan.
-Long live the Sultan.
Thank you, my Sultan.
I want only one thing in return.
Absolute loyalty.
We've been waiting for the day to be free.
Thanks Allah for letting us be free.
Amen. Amen.
He didn't mind Yakup Bey...
...or Mongolians. And he founded his beylic.
Osman Bey has earned his reputation.
We've been waiting for this for long.
Thanks to Allah. We've reached
the dream of an independent beylic.
Attention, Osman Bey!
Long live Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Well, warriors... What did you stop? Go on!
Aykut, Baysungur.
Hand out the gold to people.
-Well... Here we go.
-Osman Bey.
May Allah be pleased with you
for making us see this blessed day.
We have gifts for our Bey if you accept.
Thank you, thank you.
May it protect you from the vile
looking like the good. May it be blessed!
-Thank you.
-My Bey.
May it take your from lands to lands like the
wind. May where its shoes step on be fertile.
Praise be! Praise be!
Oh... Iltutan(his horse) shouldn't hear that.
May your sword be on the heathen's
neck all the time! May it be blessed!
Thank you, Beys of Kayi.
Thank you.
Alps!
Thank you. Thank you.
Everything will be harder than before.
The gift of ruling has been summoned!
Our flames have grown bigger.
Now we should hold the fire in our hands.
And grow the fire of battle in our heart bigger!
Now tell me.
Will you march to the whole world with me?
We will, Osman Bey!
Will you fight with me...
...until we drive the
heathens out of our homeland?
We will, Osman Bey
Will you make the world the land of Islam...
...and make the oppressed the ruling?
We will, Osman Bey!
Praise be! Praise be! Thank you.
Thank you.
We won't be the deviants.
We won't be charmed by the gold!
We will never run away..
...in hard times!
We will walk straight to spread
the words of Islam in the world!
We will!
Thank you. Thank you.
Come on then.
Join our tables now.
Well, for the sake of being a Bey...
Beys of Kayi... As the gift, 1000 horses,
...1000 weapons and 1000
goats will be given to you.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-Thank you.
May your hands be strong and your back solid.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-Thank you.
You are going to learn
about the new order tomorrow.
-Boran.
-My Bey!
Play your kopuz and entertain our hearts!
As my Beys orders.
When he reached the age of twenty...
...he received good news in his blessed dream.
Against the tyrants...
...he is the hidden giant, Osman Bey.
He carries the blood of Edebali...
...to bring pain upon the heathens.
He is the pride of Ertugrul Ghazi...
...he is a warrior like no other, Osman Bey.
He made such enemies kneel...
He rode the horses under the open skies...
...and struck down the armies of tyrants.
He is a black wolf, Osman Bey.
He struck down the armies of tyrants.
Praise be.
With the grey maned horses...
With good armor and sharp swords...
With warriors and brave hearts...
...he wrote an epic, Osman Bey.
When the gentle people cried out in pain...
He shook the earth with his call...
...to from a state..
...to from a state...
..to from a state...
...and become a home for the innocent.
He made such enemies kneel.
He rode the horses under the open skies...
...and struck down the armies of tyrants.
He is a black wolf, Osman Bey.
He struck down the armies of tyrants.
I thought you were like me, Gonca.
What are you doing, mother?
For daisies, huh?
I gave you a duty and you failed.
What is this but weakness, Gonca?
Mother.
Don't you see what kind of
dead-end you put me into?
What you call a duty...
...is my poison, mother.
Now I pull the strings.
From now on, you won't see Alaaddin.
You will get married in a short time.
What are you talking about, mother?
After your brother marries Holofira,
...you will marry someone that I find.
You'll get married when I find
someone suitable. Until that time
...you will not see Alaaddin.
Mother.
It's over.
You would crush me over..
But not this daisy, mother.
From now on, you will not see Gonca, my son.
What are you saying mother?
-Did you talk with Gonca?
-Gonca does not love you.
-Mother.
-My Alaeddin.
Maybe you were wrong, son?
Maybe your love blinded you.
And you saw your love in her eyes.
Are you saying these?
You told me to weigh with
both my heart and my mind.
I did, mother. My mind and
heart do not believe these words.
You told me to look into
her eyes. Didn't you look?
I did, however..
I did not see it.
I told you I did, mother. I saw
the tear falling from her eye.
I saw the daisies I gave
her in front of me, mother.
Let's say I saw it wrong in
her eyes, what about them?
What were they then, mother?
Alaeddin. From now on..
You will not see Gonca.
Mother. You know something else.
But you're not telling me.
Tell me.
-Mother.
-Ulgen.
Ulgen heard from Germiyanid hatuns.
Gonca loves someone else, my son.
-What?
-You heard it my son.
There is nothing we can do.
Do not get in her way.
No.
No. If you loved someone else..
You wouldn't look at me
like that, Trickster Hatun.
You wouldn't.
The issue of Aysima is closed, my son.
I sent word to his mother
with an appropriate language.
What are you saying mother? Thank Allah.
There is only one issue left.
Mother. This being a muslim thing..
Maybe you should think about it again?
My child. I already made enough concessions.
I only want one condition from you.
-Alright, mother.
-However..
If she accepted Mehmed Bey's offer..
No. Holofira..
Would never do such a thing.
If she does..
-What will you do then?
-You will see if it happens, mother.
My Orhan.
My valiant son. Tomorrow
duties will be handed out.
We are going under a great responsibility.
In a time like this, do not do any mistakes.
My mother, do not worry. I know how to convince.
Holofira will be muslim.
-If you'll excuse me now.
-You may go, my son.
I hope it would be as you said.
While we are making our move
and gaining our independence..
Enemy was not sitting around.
Byzantine is becoming allies with
Mongols to become more powerful.
Emperor's stepdaughter. Princess Maria.
She is wanted to marry with
Amir Gorklu Khan of Ilhanli.
My Bey. Byzantine is in dire, we know them.
Why are the Mongols alright with such a thing?
They started to stop us with governors..
And commanders until now.
-They did not succeed.
-However, they did not succeed.
This is how empires work.
If you do not obey, you are useless.
If you are useless..
You don't have any chance to live.
My Bey. If we do not interfere with this
marriage, they will crush us between mountains.
There were many who stroke
mountains in our bloodline.
We will take Princess Maria. Turks
won't get crushed, but mountains will.
Now, we are waiting for
news from Bayindir and Konur.
If Allah permits, they will tell us
the route of the caravan after sunrise.
Send word to bannerless.
They will come with us tomorrow.
As you command, my bey.
Tomorrow, we will have our independence.
There is no coming back from this now.
Make preparations.
Everyone who will go with the caravan is here.
However, the leader is missing.
The commander who was calling out..
Is there. Their leader should be here soon.
There is a map in front of him that he works on.
Merchant was right, route
is still not decided yet.
Let's see their leader first.
Then we will learn the route.
Master Vasilis.
Devil Veysel. What is this dog doing here?
The commander respects him.
It seems this dog is their leader.
I will have his head myself.
What is the situation, commander?
I've finished the work you wanted for the route.
On the road of Karatas the princess' caravan..
Do you really want to go
from this road, commander?
No.
She will go from this route.
This route is open for
Turks' attacks, Master Vasilis.
Do you think I don't know that? Of course I do.
However, this route is the easiest to defend.
And I already prepared
necessary precations for this.
All this, everything is for
the resurrection of Rome.
Soon, the sun will set from Turks' lands.
Feel it, commander.
The soul of Jesus Christ is with us.
Soldiers. Come with me.
Now, Bayindir Bey.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Soldiers, hurry.
They will use Iznik - Geyve route.
Thank you, Bayindir Bey.
We need to send word to Osman Bey at once.
Come on.
Where am I?
What did I do to you? What did I do to anyone?
Cerkutay. Who saved you?
Who helped you unite
with your son? You will do it.
You will do what I say.
-Shut up, shut up.
-You will be my eyes and ears at palace.
Shut up, shut up!
You were my brother. Did you
become a spy to your own palace?
-How did you do this, Cerkutay? -I did not.
What are you saying, my bey? I didn't do it.
I don't want to hear this! I don't want to!
I do not want to!
-Cerkutay?
-I don't want it.
I don't want it.
What don't you want? Cerkutay?
Wake up! It's over.
It's over. What don't you want?
-You said I don't want it.
-I died in my dream.
May Allah protect you.
-They offered houri.
-So?
-What did you say? -I said I don't want it.
-You told her that?
-I said I don't want it.
Wake up. Go away.
Get up! Sleep there.
Do you dream about houris? Go away.
You saw houri, is that so?
The enemy has started
showing his teeth already now.
That is why, Uraz Bey
go to Kite with your alps.
-Yes, my Bey.
-You will pay for food expenses
from the place you're going.
Live long, my Bey.
Thank you.
Salur Bey, Demirhan Bey.
Go to Konya area with your alps.
Yes, my Bey.
Your positions will cover your expenses.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Inhisar is yours.
It will be our outpost against the Mongol raids.
Prepare your alps, I want
Inhisar to be ready in two days.
-My Bey, you saw me fit for it but can I do it?
-Cerkutay.
Since when have you opposed your Bey's words?
Yes, my Bey.
-Orhan Bey.
-My Bey.
-You will go to Kestel.
-Yes, my Bey.
I'll go to Kestel with my
soldiers and I'll hold the borders.
But not to the borders.
You'll go to kestel and sit on the post.
Kestel is our most western land.
It will be our outpost for the conquests.
Kestel is yours from now on.
Kestel is as precious as
my life from now on, my Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
My Bey, we're talking about lands and battles
but what about trade? All the beys
trade in the frontier marketplace.
-How will we make a living?
-You're right.
You're right but do you
think we didn't think about it?
A big marketplace will be set up in Yenisehir.
It will be so big that the frontier
marketplace will look like its child.
Since Kayis are the hosts,
they will not pay any tariffs.
And alps in Yenisehir will secure the
caravans coming from the tribes around.
And Alaeddin Bey
will be leading the alps. From now on,
Alaeddin bey will control the marketplace.
Yes, my Bey.
Thank you.
-May I come in, my Bey?
-Come in.
-May I come in, my Bey? -Come in.
My Bey, we have news.
Konur informs that the Princess has come.
Everybody get back to work.
We'll get there before dark, my Princess.
Very well.
Vasilis, you mentioned about the Turks' attack.
-Have you taken measures about it?
-We have, my Princess.
The great Lords of Byzantium
deployed their soldiers.
If these barbarians try to
attack us, we will punish them.
Emir Coban, not Olcaytu Khan,
is the ruler of the Ilkhanid state.
I want you to serve the Gorklu
Khan way possible to him.
Make a wish to Erlik Khan and let
him take the Princess and come back.
Gorklu Khan will soon come, I don't
want to meet him without having anything.
I'll go and take the Princess and come back
and I leave my job to Tengri and Crusaders.
Come on!
Alps! Surround them.
-Orhan Bey.
-Let's talk, the daughter of the Lord.
What are we going to talk about? I
thought you had nothing else to say.
You didn't know me, after all.
What did you answer Mehmed?
Saadet Hatun refers to
you as my daughter-in-law.
Holofira.
-I don't want to say it, but...
-Orhan.
How could you believe what someone else says?
I haven't answered yet.
Then why Germiyanoglus are around?
-Why do they keep visiting?
I don't know how did it happen.
But there's nothing we can do anymore.
My aunt learned about everything.
-It is up to her now.
-What are you saying, Holofira?
Look at me.
Does your aunt accept it?
Not yet, but Saadet Hatun and Yakup Bey
-may convince her.
-It won't happen.
It won't happen. Holofira
say yes and become a Muslim
and we will get married right away.
Slow down, slow down, Orhan Bey.
I haven't seen you smile in a long time.
However, it suits you very well.
Holofira, I wish you said yes...
...I wish we could arrange our wedding
and others stayed away from us...
I wish you would always
smile and I could watch you.
You have beautiful dreams.
But I said my last word to
you, Orhan. I cannot be Muslim.
What if the conditions were not like this...
...if there were no obstacles,
then would you say yes to me?
Holofira... Do you love me?
Look at my face. Do not turn your eyes away.
Tell me... Do you love me, Holofira?
Love is not enough, Orhan. If my
aunt finds out about this condition...
You do. You love me but...
...you are afraid of your
aunt and my mother. Right?
Orhan... I am talking about something different.
Oghuz Alp! Take soldiers to somewhere safe.
Hatuns will come with us.
-Yes my Shahzade.
Orhan, what are you doing?
-I am abducting you
Any news from your brother?
Did he arrive in Kestel?
He must have, I guess, mother.
What happened? Are you hiding something from me?
Bala mother... My Alaeddin
brother seems lost in thought today.
Did something happen?
You are trying to
change the subject!
He is a little confused.
Go and make him happy, my Fatma.
What happened Bala?
What is wrong?
It is time for Alaeddin to get married, Malhun.
Ulgen.. Hurry.
Look... You are making a mistake, Orhan.
So that you love me, so that
you are afraid of your aunt..
...and scared of my mother, then
we know the solution, Holofira.
The solution is to abduct you.
Come on, Holofira. Come on.
Orhan, look. If my aunt finds out...
-If your aunt finds out...
...she cannot do anything. Come on.
Karaali! -My Shahzade!
To Kestel! -Yes my Shahzade.
We are going to our new home.
Where did this dog come from?
The caravan was supposed to
go to Mongols. But they came.
Commander Karacelasun.
What happened? Couldn't you wait?
We were going to bring the Princess to you.
I can do it on my own, Crusader.
These lands are not safe.
I do not trust your weak soldiers who
cannot even protect their own lands.
If we do not take Princess to Gorklu
Khan, he will take us to death. Come on.
Alright, Mongol. As you say.
Boran! -My Bey!
-We will attack from the top with the archers.
-Yes my Bey.
We will destroy them all when the caravan stops.
Yes my Bey.
Turahan. -My Bey.
The caravan is approaching.
Karacelasun also joined them.
We came here to take the Princess. In this
case, we will also take Karacelasun's head.
Come on, Alps!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
First, Beylic, now the marketplace, huh?
Osman Bey is not going to stop.
He wants to prevent the trades
in the frontiers marketplace
...by setting up a marketplace in Yenisehir.
So? What are you going to do now, Yakub Sultan?
Kanyumaz! -My Sultan..
Prepare the gifts.
We will go and give our
warm wishes to Osman Bey.
Yes, my Sultan. -Warm wishes?
But we thought you would get angry.
That's what Osman Bey wants. To enrage me.
But... it won't happen.
Beys... these lands...
...need more trades.
Now we will go and say
"Congratulations" to Osman Bey. Come on.
Suleyman Bey!
Were you single?
-Yes, Yakup Bey.
Starting a family is important, Suleyman Bey.
You are late.
You must have started your family
before you sat on the chair of Beylic.
This was my fate, my Yakup Sultan.
Can I come in, my Sultan? -Come in.
My Sultan. We received news from our spies.
Byzantine is sending a
Princess to Mongols to
become allies but Osman
Bey is also aware of that.
I hope Osman does not get us into trouble again.
Come on Beys. We will go
to Osman Bey's marketplace.
Princess, don't be afraid. I'm here.
Horsemen! Ambush! Fight!
Protect the princess!
It's time for you to rise, alps.
This attack will be your death firman!
If it were a real firman, it
would be! But it won't be!
I will kill whoever releases the princess!
Vasilis!
Where are you going? You have a life to give!
Osman, I missed you.
You say so? Come to me.
Come here. Come.
You can't kill us. Souls are immortal, Osman.
I feel sorry for you. You will
never live in peace in these lands.
-Never.
-You say?
You think you can destroy us?
Whenever there is a Pharaoh, we will be Moses.
Whenever there is cruelty,
...we will shield the innocent.
You think you can destroy us?
Get up. Get up
Get up
Up!
We..
Let me meet my God. Come on.
...die one and rise a thousand!
Take the princess!
You can't take the princess before you kill me.
-I will take your head too.
-Take the princess!
Or Gorklu Khan's wrath will rain on us!
It's too late to take the princess.
We are drawing back.
Do you show your dagger to
everyone trying to save you, Princess?
You aren't saving me, Barbarian
Turk! Get your hands off!
Now you've got rid of your
thorns, Princess. Move!
Princess Maria.
They are playing politic games through you.
This is against us. For this reason,
...you will be our guest for a while.
-You can't get away with this.
-Princess.
Aykurt! Take Princess to Sogut.
As you order, my Bey.
The Bannerless will be with you as well.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
We're going to Yenisehir. Those who heard
about the market must have left for Yenisehir.
As you order, my Bey.
Let's go, alps!
I told you to place them orderly! Look at this.
Place them again! How many more times should
I tell you how important this market is?
Calm down. You'll burn the
whole market with your fire, brother.
My heart is burning, sister.
Both my mind and heart are confused.
Brother, Gonca Hatun's tongue tells the truth.
Nobody else's words can't
save you from this trouble.
Gonca is mute to me, Fatma.
Maybe, my mother is right.
Maybe I should stay away from her.
You say so, but my Allah doesn't want so.
This is your destiny, brother. Go talk to her.
I'm too busy, sister.
Look at that. Curious Saadet is here.
-She would never miss this.
-Let's go welcome her.
Ulgen, talk to Gonca.
Alaaddin won't see her again.
It'd be inappropriate for me to talk.
I shouldn't disturb them anymore.
Welcome, Saadet Hatun. I
wasn't expecting to see you.
Why wouldn't I come?
I thought you might need some advice.
You know how skillful I am at the market.
How thoughtful you are.
Let's walk around the market then.
Gonca, we need to talk.
Orhan... Orhan, please listen to me.
This is your room, Lord's daughter. Come on.
Orhan, listen! Please don't do this.
Don't. Send us back before someone hears.
-This won't end up good.
-This will end up good.
It will be very good,
Holofira. I planned everything.
You are putting both of us in danger.
You don't know my aunt.
Your aunt doesn't know
me either, Holofira. Look.
I'm doing everything for us.
For our future. There is no going back.
-Come on.
-How many more times should I tell you?
I won't be a Muslim. We can't get married.
You have everything you need here, Holofira.
If you need anything, alps
will be beside your door.
You can tell them, and
they will do it. Come on now.
Orhan, listen to me.
Orhan listen to me for once. Don't do this.
I know how to warm your heart towards Islam.
You are a good person, Gonca Hatun. You
did what I said and ruined your trickery.
You don't know anything Ulgen.
Do you think I did that
trickery because I wanted?
I am the last person to wish harm to Alaeddin.
Look here.
Do you.. Do you really
love Alaeddin Bey for real?
The heart wants what it wants.
You love him.
I know it is impossible. I know it won't work.
Gonca. I did something.
I did such a thing. But I had to.
When Bala Hatun told me to speak..
Did you tell that to Alaeddin?
I said Gonca Hatun loves someone else.
Ulgen what did you do?
I don't know. I couldn't have said the truth.
That was the first thing that came to my mind.
Bala Hatun, did she tell that to Alaeddin?
No. I mean, I don't know.
However, even if she didn't, she will tell soon.
She looked at me angrily.
I need to tell him before Bala Hatun does.
Gonca. Will you really tell everything?
I did the mistake. Let
him learn all of it from me.
-Can you call Alaeddin to there?
-Yes.
-Do not worry, I will tell him now.
-Alright, come on.
So you caused all this Ulgen.
When Saadet Hatun hears
this she will show you what it is.
Praise be! Praise be! It is alright, even
not as much as frontier marketplace.
As always, I will buy the first stall.
It seems frontier marketplace is
not enough for you, Saadet Hatun.
Trade needs competition, Bala Hatun.
Yenisehir Marketplace is good. This way
frontier marketplace will be more valuable.
Since you want to buy the first stall,
pick any place you want, Saadet Hatun.
Even though you gave us the most silent corner.
Do you think your rugs and
my goods are the same, Malhun?
Of course, the most
magnificent stall will be mine.
You're also right, Saadet Hatun.
The trade going on in
Yenisehir is not like any other.
Thanks to us, you attract buyers
to frontier marketplace, right?
Now, if you'll excuse me hatuns.
I will go around the marketplace.
Let me see where..
The most magnificent stall is.
-Go, have a look.
Amir Gorklu Khan.
You couldn't get revenge from Osman..
Now you let them took the Princess.
Until my soul leaves my body..
I will have Osman's head!
You ran away from Osman.
You left the Princess.
You seeing eyes..
Will not see anymore.
You souls..
Will reach to Tamu(hell)!
My enemy becomes the earth itself.
Their blood spills, becomes a river!
The death of my nokers..
Becomes a legend!
The brave lives on!
Gorklu Khan I will get her.
I will get Osman and the Princess!
You are as incapable as not
even getting your own revenge.
You put the might of IIhanli
under the boots of Osman.
Amir Gorklu Khan. Osman's
alps are taking Princess to Sogut.
Gorklu Khan. Sogut is the first city of Kayi.
Allow me to get the Princess
and my revenge from Osman!
Osman is my enemy now!
His head is mine!
However, he must not reach the
other world without getting revenge.
You will have your revenge for your services.
Get up.
They had me unsheathe my sword.
Now the cold will be washed with blood!
We will have the heads of those who rebel!
Strong Amir! Strong Amir!
I will tell him.
He might think I am a bad
person. He will learn everything.
Trickster Hatun.
Alaeddin Bey.
Last time you rejected me. Now
you sent me a note to invite me.
Why? Did taking a few steps tire you?
I used to come everytime you invited me.
And I never said I was tired.
-And with one time..
-No.
Even if you invited me behind
the Mount Qaf, I would still come.
You would, but why do you look
at me that way, Alaeddin Bey?
I heard something.
I am trying to get my answer from your eyes.
Gonca...
-They told me you love someone e...
-No.
They were wrong.
I don't love anyone.
Anyone, huh?
If there is no one... Do you also not love me...
Alaeddin Bey.. -No.
Call me Scholar.
I didn't like "Alaeddin Bey".
Good.
Scholar...
I want to talk to you.
Talk, Trickster Hatun. Talk to me.
But... answer my question first.
So that there is no one else,
then why did you reject me?
Now we are talking about...
First look into my eyes and
answer my question, Coy Hatun.
What changed in one day and you gave
me an answer which was similar to a poison?
Gonca... Look at my eyes.
I don't need another answer when
you are looking at me like that but...
Alaeddin Bey...
Do not expect that answer from me.
I have different answers to give you.
Alaeddin...
I... listened to my mother and...
-Gonca.
Mother!
Saadet Hatun...
Didn't I tell you not to talk to Alaeddin again?
Pull yourself together! The one
standing in front of you is your daughter!
Alaeddin Bey! Don't you..
...approach my daughter again!
My Allah, give me patience.
Osman Bey is coming!
For Gorklu Khan..
What is happening there?
Move! What is happening?
Brother... Mongol soldier...
There is a spy! Alps! Take our people inside!
The end of the jackal who gets
in the cave of wolves is death!
Protect our people! Come on! Inside!
The darkness brought death to
Sogut! Whoever stands before him dies!
Alps! Go to Yenisehir! Inform Osman Bey! Go!
You will be burnt alive!
Take the Princess! Burn the rest of them...
...to teach everyone a lesson!
Peace be upon you. May it be easy.
-Peace be upon you too.
- May you earn well.
Thank you, my Bey. Welcome.
So... Tell me, how much is this?
My Bey, we are making these
shoes with the black goatskin.
Every part of it is fine workmanship.
We sell it for three coins.
Three coins? -Yes my Bey.
Isn't this too cheap?
My Bey... You opened a source
of income for us in the marketplace.
And we sell at a lower profit.
Our Alaeddin Bey also
set measures. It is forbidden
for us to sell it for
higher than 5 coins.
Good, good.
May it be easy. -Thank you. May Allah bless you.
My son... Did you set limits for everything?
I did, my Bey. In this way, we are
providing equality and preventing cheating.
Thank you. The state is a whole.
If the merchant's balance is not off, not
even a stone will touch the Alp's feet in war.
Thank you. You did the right thing.
Thank you my Bey. I appreciate it.
Let's go to this counter. Malhun..
Check these..
-Welcome.
-Thank you, may it be easy.
It's all hand woven. They are very
beautiful. Thanks to your hands.
Osman Bey!
We invited you to the opening
of the frontiers marketplace.
Why didn't you invite us?
What happened, Yakup Bey?
The marketplace is still new.
If it was the right time
to invite you, we would.
What happened? Why did you come here?
You are declaring a sovereign Beylic
on the lands where there is a Sultan.
Isn't it normal for me to come
here and stand before you?
When were we afraid of
those who stood before us?
Tell me... What brought you here?
The reason why I came here..
-Yes?
They are going to the dungeon!
They can! The dungeon will be their grave!
Where are you going, Mongol dogs?
I kill those who dare to take what is mine!
Attack until Sogut is burnt down!
Sogut will be safe, and you will be destroyed!
Your brave words will
make your death come faster!
-You pathetic dastard!
-Hit, bannerless, hit!
Ruin the oppressors!
Our same and our da'wah is the same!
Hit bannerless, hit!
Brother!
Come on, let's go to the
dungeon to save the Princess.
One shall be in sorrow, pursuing a cure,
Is he in love if he does
not seek a way to endure?
O' Yunus, embrace the pain of your friend,
Is he in love if no arrow
of love in him is penned?
-Peace be upon you, Yunus Emre
-Peace be upon you too.
You've brought joy, Orhan Bey.
I hope it is not a wrong time.
There is a very important issue.
-I ask for your help, Yunus Emre.
-Astagfirullah.
If I have a cure, I will
give it to you for sure.
-Thank you.
-Here.
Have a seat.
My mother will only agree to our
marriage if Holofira becomes a Muslim.
And I want her to be a Muslim so
we can be together in both worlds.
But I can't convince Holofira.
Yunus Emre, I want you
to make Holofira love Islam.
There is only One Maker, Orhan Bey.
There is only One Who can make someone love.
A person does not believe
when we want her to believe.
-It happens when she wants it.
-She doesn't want it.
I don't know what to do, Yunus Emre.
Your words are so effective.
When we first met, even Holofira
was fascinated by your words.
So what I mean is that you have
the cure for my problem, Yunus Emre.
-The Messenger of Allah...
-Peace be upon him.
...tried to talk his uncle Ebu Talib...
...into believing.
You know, his uncle...
...even after all those persistence...
...chose to believe his ancestors' religion.
And love...
His uncle was as precious as his own life
for our Prophet (PBUH).
That's why, he said that
he'll keep making requests for
him as long is it is not forbidden.
And Allah sent a verse upon this,
and said
"You surely cannot guide whoever you like,
but it is Allah Who guides whoever He wills
and He knows best who are fit to be guided."
While there were so many people...
...that did not believe in The
Messenger of Allah's (PBUH) words...
...what effect can our words have?
Surely He owns all the hearts.
So you're saying, Yunus Emre
that "just sit and wait," is that so?
No. A Muslim does not wait.
He always makes an effort.
But you want us to talk to her about Islam,
let's talk about it with the
language of state, not words.
Let us tell it like how our Prophet (PBUH) did.
Otherwise, it is easy to
sit and talk about heaven and hell.
It is easy to talk about Islam.
The important thing is to become a Muslim.
Can we become one?
Can we have the manners that our Prophet had?
Is our sincerity in worship his sincerity?
That's why we will look at these
things first, we will talk about it later.
First, Holofira will see a Muslim
and she will want to know about Islam.
She will want to listen so that she can hear.
If not, everything we say
will be nonsense for her.
It's up to you to make Holofira want it.
It's up to me
to make Holofira want it.
Thank you, Yunus Emre.
I'm here to
congratulate you
about your sovereign Beylic
and marketplace, Osman Bey.
Bring the gifts.
Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Thank you, Yakup Bey.
The fact that you're not my Bey anymore
does not make us enemies, Osman Bey.
We want our people to exist.
We want the same thing for you, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
My Bey, Mongols attacked
Sogut to take the Princess.
What?
Princess.
What happened, Osman Bey?
It's not well, Yakup Bey.
Mongol dogs raided Sogut.
Now they will be treated with our furor.
Alps!
Come on.
Visit turkision.com for more!